mtggoldfish.com 2019-05-08

# Privacy Policy & Terms of Use

**Browse >** Home / Company / Privacy Policy 

## MTGGoldfish Privacy Policy

Updated May 25, 2018, Version 1.2

Welcome to the MTGGoldfish Website. The MTGGoldfish Website is owned and operated by MTGGoldfish Inc., a Delaware Company, based in California. (MTGGoldfish). This Privacy Policy governs the use of the MTGGoldfish Website. When using or accessing the MTGGoldfish Website, you are agreeing to be bound to the terms within this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use policy. This policy may refer to users as “you” or “user” and may refer to MTGGoldfish as “us,” “we,” or “our.” _If you do not agree to the terms within this Privacy Policy and the correspondingTerms of Use, do not access or use the MTGGoldfish Website._

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your personal information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use our website and services.

### INFORMATION STORED BY MTGGOLDFISH

In order to carry out the services of MTGGoldfish and to provide a great user experience, we will collect and store the following information about you:

**_Personal Information, that may be used to identify you as an individual (Personal information is any information related to an identified or identifiable natural person)._ **

  1. First and Last Name;
  2. Username
  3. Profile Picture or Avatar;
  4. Profile Information from Third-Party Social Media and Payment Websites;
  5. Your Email Address;
  6. IP Address

**_Other information that may be linked to personal information._ **

  1. Content You Post Publicly or Privately on Your MTGGoldfish Account;
  2. Searches Completed through the Website;
  3. Preference Settings;
  4. Stored Information or Files Created or Stored on Website Through Your Account;
  5. Any Emails You Send to MTGGoldfish;
  6. Domain Name;
  7. Times of Access to Website;
  8. Website that Referred to MTGGoldfish;
  9. Your Operating System Type

### HOW WE COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.

MTGGoldfish collects personal information from you upon your registration for our services and/or account creation. We collect any additional information about you when you interact with us electronically or in person, when you access our website and when we provide our services to you.

It may not be readily apparent to you when such data is being collected. For instance, when you visit our website, your IP address is collected so that we know where to send information you are requesting. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet. 

### WHY WE COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.

We process your personal information because we have a contractual obligation with you. Once you create an account to use our website, application and services, and agree to our terms of service, a contract is formed between you and us. In order to carry out our contractual obligations we need to process the information you provide, which also includes personal information.

Even if there is no direct contractual obligation between us, we may process your information based on your explicit consent you have provided (to us or a third party data controller) for the processing of that information.

### HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.

We will use the personal information collected from you:

  * to administer your account with us and provide you with our services;
  * to respond to your inquiries and deliver reminder e-mails to you;
  * to provide you with information regarding updates and changes to our Website, our Terms of Service or any services we offer or provide through it;
  * to improve our product and services;
  * to provide personalised experience for you upon use of our services;

Additionally we may use anonymized information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

### HOW LONG WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION.

We will keep your personal information for as long as you use our website and services.

You have the right to request that your personal information is permanently removed from our system and database at any time. You can e-mail such requests for permanent removal to contact@mtggoldfish.com. The requests will be accommodated within seven days.

### DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION.

We will not disclose your personal information to any third parties, however, we reserve the right to disclose information about you to third-parties for assistance in improving the MTGGoldfish products and services. MTGGoldfish may also disclose information about you to third-parties where we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of MTGGoldfish, our affiliates or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements and our terms of use); (ii) protect the safety, privacy, and security of users of the MTGGoldfish employees, owners, or members of the public; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; (iv) comply with the law or legal process; or (v) respond to requests from public and government authorities.

The Website allows users to login through their Facebook and Twitter accounts. The Facebook and Twitter privacy policies, including the data Facebook and Twitter collects and the uses of that data, is beyond our control, and we take no responsibility for Facebook’s or Twitter’s practices. Before you submit any personal information to Facebook or Twitter, we recommend that you read Facebook’s and Twitter’s privacy policies, which can be found at the following links: <https://www.facebook.com/policies> and <https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en>. MTGGoldfish uses third-party payment processor Paypal for all transactions. Please visit the Paypal website for their privacy and terms of use policies as all payment transactions are governed by them. 

### COOKIES AND TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES.

We may collect information about you using "cookies." Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. Usually the information that we collect automatically through cookies is statistical data and cannot be used to identify you as an individual. It helps us to improve our website and to deliver a better and more personalized service.

When you first visit our site, we ask you whether you wish us to use cookies. If you choose not to accept them, we shall not use them for your visit except to record that you have not consented to their use for any other purpose. If you choose not to use cookies or you prevent their use through your browser settings, you will not be able to use all the functionality of our site.

### SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.

MTGGoldfish is committed to ensuring that the information you provide to us is secure from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. We have implemented suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure information and protect it from misuse, interference, loss and unauthorized access, modification and disclosure.

  * All information you provide to us is stored on our secure database behind a Virtual Private Network;
  * All passwords are stored in an encrypted form;
  * We restrict access to personal information to employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination, if they fail to meet these obligations;
  * We back up all client data in multiple data centers enabling speedy recovery in case of a disaster;
  * Whenever possible we will make sure we pseudonymise all personal or related data.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.

### COMMERICAL AND NON-COMMERICAL COMMUNICATION

By providing information to the Website, such as signing up for a newsletter or an account, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited email from MTGGoldfish since you have agreed to such communication by providing your information to MTGGoldfish. However, you may unsubscribe from certain communications by notifying MTGGoldfish that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information. MTGGoldfish will remove you from the database where you have the right to request this under the Privacy Policy, Terms of Use, or applicable law, or where MTGGoldfish voluntarily decides to grant the request.

### CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT

The MTGGoldfish Website is directed to adults, over the age of 18. MTGGoldfish does not knowingly collect information from children under 13 years of age or have any reasonable grounds for believing that persons under the age of 13 are accessing the Website. If MTGGoldfish discovers any inadvertently collected Personal Information of a person under the age of 13, that information will be swiftly deleted from its records. If you believe that MTGGoldfish may have any information from a person under age 13, please contact MTGGoldfish at contact@mtggoldfish.com.

### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

MTGGoldfish welcomes residents of the State of California to use its Website, and complies with the California Business and Professions Code §§ 22575-22579. If you are a California resident you may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Please send a written request to MTGGoldfish, Inc., PO BOX 1972, Burlingame, CA, 94011.

Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the Californian privacy statutes. If you have any questions contact MTGGoldfish, contact@mtggoldfish.com.

### USER ACCESS AND CONTROL

If you would like to access, review, correct, update, suppress, or otherwise limit our use of your personal information you have previously provided directly to us, you may contact us at contact@mtggoldfish.com. In your request, please include your email address, name, address, and telephone number and specify clearly what information you would like to access, change, update, or suppress. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time. If we change our privacy policy, we will notify you via email sent to the email address you provide at the time of registration as well as post an updated version of this Privacy Policy on our website so that you and other users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Changes will not apply retroactively and changes addressing new functions for a service or changes made for legal reasons will be effective immediately. If you do not agree to the modified terms, you should discontinue your use of the Website. Your continued use of the after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of the new Privacy Policy. You should also check back from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes.

### CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions, comments, complaints or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you can contact us anytime through at the following address: contact@mtggoldfish.com. We take complaints very seriously and will respond shortly after receiving written notice of your complaint.
